Guide to the Research Institute for the Study of Man (RISM) Vertical Files RISM.VF.1
New York University Archives
- Haiti (Box 12)
  - Haiti: Voodooism (Box 13)
    - Ritual Performance and Religious Experience: A Service for the Gods in Southern Haiti, 1978; RISM 21097; Lowenthal, Ira P.; p. 392-414. (Box 13)
    - The Influence of Voodoo on the Lives of the Haitian People, undated; RISM 24074; Isaac, Acelius E.; p. 2-10. (Box 13)
    - The Invisibles, by Francis Huxley; Review, 1966; RISM 24174; Mintz, Sidney W. (Sidney Wilfred), 1922-2015; p. 582-583. (Box 13)
    - Haitian Voodoo in the Eighteenth Century: Language, Culture, Resistance, 1991; RISM 26884; Geggus, David Patrick; p. 21-51. (Box 13)
    - American Possessions: Hurston and Dunham on Haiti, 2002; RISM 27408; Pettinger, Alasdair, 1959-; 8 pages; 8.0 (Box 13)
    - Les Survivances du Totemisme dans le Vodou Haitien, 1967; RISM 21085; Oriol, Jacques; 32 pages (Box 13)
    - Bizango: A Voodoo Secret Society in Haiti, undated; Laguerre, Michel S. (Box 13)
  - Haiti: Voodooism, Bibliography (Box 13)
    - Etudes sur le Vodou Haitien: Bibliographie Analytique, 1979; RISM 24943; Laguerre, Michel S.; various paging. (Box 13)
      Voodooism.; Haiti; Bibliography.
- Hispaniola (Box 13)
  - Hispaniola: Cultural Pluralism (Box 13)
    - Cultural Dichotomy in the Island of Hispaniola, 1952; RISM 17645; Crist, Raymond E.; p. 105-122. (Box 13)
      Cultural pluralism.; Hispaniola.
  - Hispaniola: Excavations, Archaeology (Box 13)
    - From Contact to Criollos: The Archaeology of Spanish Colonization in Hispaniola, 1993; RISM 25185; Deagan, Kathleen A.; p. 67-103. (Box 13)
      Hispaniola.; Excavations (Archaeology).
- Israel (Box 13)
  - Israel: Arabs (Box 13)
    - The Class Situation of the Arab National Minority in Israel, 1978; RISM 21099; Rosenfeld, Henry; p. 374-407. (Box 13)
      Israel.; Arabs.
    - Non-Hierarchical, Hierarchical and Masked Reciprocity in an Arab Village, 1974; RISM 21101; Rosenfeld, Henry; p. 139-166. (Box 13)
    - Processes of Structural Change Within the Arab Village Extended Family, 1958; RISM 21100; Rosenfeld, Henry; p. 1127-1139. (Box 13)
      Arabs.; Israel.
    - Social Changes in an Arab Village, 1959; RISM 21098; Rosenfeld, Henry; 16 pages; February-March 1959; April-May 1959 (Box 13)
    - Human Evolution in Contemporary Communities, 1954; RISM 18436; Lasker, Gabriel Ward; p. 353-363. (Box 12)
  - Israel: Family (Box 13)
    - Social Structure and Family Size, 1959; RISM 18396; Ṭalmon-Gerber, Yoninah; p. 121-145. (Box 13)
      Israel.; Family.
    - Social Change and Family Structure, 1963; RISM 18398; Ṭalmon-Gerber, Yoninah; p. 468-487. (Box 13)
      Family.; Israel.
    - The Privatization of Public Means, the State-Made Middle Class and the Realization of Family Value in Israel, 1976; RISM 23207; Rosenfeld, Henry; p. 131-159. (Box 13)
- Jamaica
  - Jamaica: Adolescence (Box 13)